#This file should be read by cycling through and adding new objects every pass.
#The order of passes should be:
#				1) <Person>
#				2) <Item>
#				3) <Action>
#				4) <Relationship>
#				5) <Location>
#				6) <StoryValues>
#
# The formatting of each type should be as follows:
# <Action>
# <Item> NameOfPersonHolding(NULL for World)    NameOfObject
# <Person> Name    Gender(0 male, 1 female)
# <Relationship> NameOfMain    NameOfPartner    Type    Strength
# <StoryValues> PoliceRep MobRep PoliceWantedLevel MobWantedLevel
#
#	Parent=0, Child=1, Sibling=2, Married=3, Family=4, SO=5, Strangers=6,
#	Friends=7, Enemies=8, Teacher=9, Student=10, Working=11, Community=12
#
#	0=bad, 1=average, 2=good
#
# To give attributes to a person, list all items, relationships, and actions after them
# Example:	Nick holding a banana in a relationship with Nikki
#			<Person>Nick 0
#			<Item>Banana
#			<Relationship>Nikki 3 1
#

#Define all items here. Included all actions that it can do and can happen to it here
<Item>Knife
<Action>cut do
<Action>break get
<Item>Apple
<Action>cut get
<Item>Carrot
<Action>cut get

#Define People here. Included all items, actions, and relationships after the person
<Person>Nick  0
<StoryValues> 9 0 0 2
<Action>eat do
<Action>stab get
<Item>Knife 
<Item>Doughnut
<Item>GlassWater
<Relationship>Nikki 6 2
<Location>Town Square 

<Person>Nikki 1
<StoryValues> 1 1 1 1
<Item>Stethoscope
<Relationship>Nick 3 1